[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section 3
您好，欢迎来到第3节
of lesson 2. In this part of the course we're going to talk about
在第2课中，我们将讨论
how you can work with streams of objects and also streams
如何使用对象流以及流
primitive types in Java.
Java中的基本类型。
If we look at the Java language it's not
如果我们看看Java语言，那不是
truly object-oriented. In order to
真正的面向对象。为了
improve performance, rather than treating absolutely everything
提高性能，而不是绝对对待一切
in Java as an object, we have primitives types.
在Java中，作为对象，我们有基本类型。
so they're bytes, shorts, ints, longs,
所以它们是字节，短裤，整数，多头
doubles, floats, and Chars that we can use and
双打，浮点数和我们可以使用的字符
there's also boolean as well, that we can use
还有布尔值，我们可以使用
to represent primitive values and
代表原始值
if we want to use those primitives values with certain type of classes,
如果我们想在某些类型的类中使用这些原始值，
particularly collections, then we do need to convert them into
特别是收藏，那么我们需要将它们转换为
objects rather than the primitive representation.
对象而不是原始表示。
So we have the equivalent classes, the wrapper classes as they're called,
因此，我们有等效的类，即所谓的包装器类，
for each of those primitive types. So there is a Byte class, a Short class, an
对于每个原始类型。因此，有一个Byte类，一个Short类，一个
Integer class and so on.
整数类等。
In terms of how we use that we can explicitly create
在使用方式方面，我们可以明确创建
objects at those types in our code and we can explicitly retrieve the values
代码中那些类型的对象，我们可以显式检索值
from those
从那些
objects if we want to, but
对象，如果我们想要，但是
while ago there was a some improvements made around Java
之前有一些关于Java的改进
so we added what's called auto boxing and unboxing.
因此我们添加了自动装箱和拆箱功能。
This means that if the compiler can determine that
这意味着如果编译器可以确定
what you're actually doing is using primitive value
您实际上正在使用原始值
where an object representation needs to be used
需要使用对象表示的地方
then it will create an object instance for you
然后它将为您创建一个对象实例
of that wrapper class passing in the value as the parameter to the constructor.
包装类的类，将值作为参数传递给构造函数。
If it can tell that where you need something
如果它可以告诉您您需要什么
as a primitive value and you actually have an object representation it will
作为原始值，实际上您有一个对象表示形式
automatically
自动地
unbox it and extract the value for you. This leads us to
取消装箱并为您提取价值。这导致我们
needing to understand somethings about how streams work.
需要了解有关流如何工作的一些知识。
Because if we had a stream,
因为如果我们有一个流，
by default everything is an object. So we have a stream that
默认情况下，所有内容都是对象。所以我们有一个流
we create from a source, which will be a stream of objects, let's say from the
我们从一个源创建，该源将是一个对象流，比如说从
collection.
采集。
So in this example here what we're doing is we're
因此，在此示例中，我们正在做的是
taking collection of students and we create a stream. We then pass that into
收集学生，我们创建了一个流。然后，我们将其传递给
filter to look to see whether the graduation year is 2015
筛选以查看毕业年份是否为2015
and then we pass that collection of objects
然后我们传递对象集合
into map. At that point
进入地图。在那时候
what we're going do is we're going to retrieve the score
我们要做的是检索分数
of that student, but here we have a little bit of an issue because
那个学生的名字，但是这里有一个问题，因为
the score that we're retrieving from the student is actually going to be
我们从学生那里获得的分数实际上是
an int, so it's a primitive value. getScore
一个int，所以它是一个原始值。 getScore
is defined signature as returning an int, not an Integer
被定义为返回一个整数，而不是一个整数的签名
wrapper object. So it returns an int.
包装对象。因此它返回一个整数。
That gives usa little bit of a problem because when we do the map
这给美国带来了一点问题，因为当我们绘制地图时
what's going to happen is that we return an int
将会发生的是，我们返回一个整数
from getScore and in order for that to become stream of
从getScore并为了使其成为
objects the stream then has to
流必须具有的对象
auto-box those ints into Integer
自动将这些int装箱为Integer
objects to create a stream of Integers. When we pass that stream of Integer
对象来创建整数流。当我们通过整数流时
objects to max, max actually needs to look at the values,
最大对象，最大实际需要查看值，
so max has then got to do the reverse. It's got to
因此max必须做相反的事情。一定要
unbox each of those Integer objects to get at the
解开每个这些Integer对象的框，以获取
value and that's an awful lot of work, so we creating objects that we don't need.
价值，这是一项艰巨的工作，因此我们创建了不需要的对象。
Passing them to a method which is then simply can't take the values
将它们传递给然后无法采用值的方法
out of them and use those values to get round that problem.
并使用这些值来解决该问题。
What we've done with streams is to provide
我们对流所做的是提供
3 particular type-specific,
3种特定于类型的特定信息，
or primitive type specific I should say of stream.
或特定于原始类型的流。
so there is an IntStream, a DoubleStream and a LongStream.
因此有一个IntStream，一个DoubleStream和一个LongStream。
we haven't bothered with ByteStream or ShortStream or anything like that because
我们没有为ByteStream或ShortStream或类似的东西而烦恼
those can be represented
那些可以代表
by either an IntStream or LongStream.
通过IntStream或LongStream。
What we can do with these is we can change the way things work
我们可以做的就是改变工作方式
in terms of our code. If we go back to an example now
根据我们的代码。如果我们现在回到一个例子
we pass the set of students who graduated in the year
我们通过了当年毕业的学生
2015 into mapToInt.
2015年纳入mapToInt。
What that will do is it will actually, rather than creating
那将是实际要做的，而不是创造
stream of objects, which are the integer values
对象流，它们是整数值
boxed into Integer objects,
装在整数对象中
it will create stream of ints. It will create
它将创建整数流。它将创建
stream of primitive values. Therefore we don't need to do
基本值流。因此，我们不需要做
any boxing or unboxing, because when the pass it to max
任何装箱或拆箱，因为当传递给最大
what's going to happen is it has a stream of
将会发生的事情是
primitives values, so can simply evaluate those to find the maximum value.
原始值，因此可以简单地评估那些值以找到最大值。
It doesn't have to unbox things in order to get the values
不必为了获得值而拆箱
as they go through.  To summarise Section 3,
当他们经历。总结第3节，
because Java has both primitive types
因为Java具有两种原始类型
as well as object types, when we deal with streams
以及对象类型，当我们处理流时
we need to have the ability to represent certain
我们需要有能力代表某些
primitive types of streams. And as I said, there are three of those: IntStream,
流的原始类型。正如我所说，其中有三个：IntStream，
DoubleStream and LongStream. When you want to use those
DoubleStream和LongStream。当你想使用那些
you can use method like mapToInt,
您可以使用诸如mapToInt之类的方法，
mapToDouble or mapToLong. There's also other
mapToDouble或mapToLong。还有其他
methods so if you have a stream, let's say you have an IntStream
方法，如果您有一个流，假设您有一个IntStream
and you want to convert it to a stream objects for whatever reason
并且无论出于何种原因，您都希望将其转换为流对象
put in a collection, you do mapToObj, so that you can go both ways.
在集合中，您可以执行mapToObj，这样您就可以双向进行。
There's very effective ways
有很有效的方法
of processing both object representations and
处理对象表示和
primitive streams in the stream API and that is the end
流API中的原始流，到此为止
of section 3.
第3节。